("Where Is The Love"
by The Black Eyed Peas)
♪ What's wrong with the world mama ♪
♪ People livin' like
they ain't got no mamas ♪
♪ I think the whole world's
addicted to the drama ♪
♪ Only attracted to the things
that'll bring the trauma ♪
♪ Overseas yeah we tryin'
to stop terrorism ♪
♪ But we still got
terrorists here livin' ♪
♪ In the USA the big CIA ♪
♪ The Bloods and The Crips and the KKK ♪
♪ But if you only have
love for your own race ♪
♪ Then you only leave
space to discriminate ♪
♪ And to discriminate
only generates hate ♪
♪ And when you hate then you're
bound to get irate yeah ♪
♪ Madness is what you demonstrate ♪
♪ And that's exactly how
anger works and operates ♪
♪ Man you gotta have love
this'll set us straight ♪
♪ Take control of your mind and meditate ♪
♪ Let your soul gravitate
to the love y'all y'all ♪
♪ People killin' people dyin' ♪
♪ Children hurt and you hear them cryin' ♪
♪ Can you practice what you preach ♪
♪ And would you turn the other cheek ♪
♪ Father Father Father help us ♪
♪ Send some guidance from above ♪
♪ 'Cause people got me
got me questioning ♪
♪ Where is the love love ♪
♪ Where is the love ♪
♪ Where is the love the love the love ♪
♪ It just ain't the same
old ways have changed ♪
♪ New days are strange
is the world insane ♪
♪ If love and peace is so strong ♪
♪ Why are there pieces of
love that don't belong ♪
♪ Nations droppin' bombs ♪
♪ Chemical gasses fillin'
lungs of little ones ♪
♪ With ongoin' sufferin'
as the youth die young ♪
♪ So ask yourself is
the lovin' really gone ♪
♪ So I could ask myself
really what is goin' wrong ♪
♪ In this world that we livin'
in people keep on givin' in ♪
♪ Makin' wrong decisions only
visions of them dividends ♪
♪ Not respectin' each
other deny thy brother ♪
♪ A war is goin' on but
the reason's undercover ♪
♪ The truth is kept secret
and swept under the rug ♪
♪ If you never know truth
then you never know love ♪
♪ Where's the love y'all
come on I don't know ♪
♪ Where's the truth y'all
♪ Where's the love y'all ♪
♪ People killin' people dyin' ♪
♪ Children hurt and you hear them cryin' ♪
♪ Can you practice what you preach ♪
♪ And would you turn the other cheek ♪
♪ Father Father Father help us ♪
♪ Send some guidance from above ♪
♪ 'Cause people got me
got me questioning ♪
♪ Where is the love love ♪
♪ Where is the love ♪
♪ Where is the love the love the love ♪
♪ I feel the weight of
the world on my shoulder ♪
♪ As I'm gettin' older
y'all people gets colder ♪
♪ Most of us only care
about money makin' ♪
♪ Selfishness got us followin'
the wrong direction ♪
♪ Wrong information always
shown by the media ♪
♪ Negative images is the main criteria ♪
♪ Infecting the young minds
faster than bacteria ♪
♪ Kids wanna act like what
they see in the cinema ♪
♪ Yo' whatever happened to
the values of humanity ♪
♪ Whatever happened to the
fairness and equality ♪
♪ Instead of spreading love
we're spreading animosity ♪
♪ Lack of understanding
leading us away from unity ♪
♪ That's the reason why
sometimes I'm feelin' under ♪
sometimes I'm feelin' down ♪
♪ There's no wonder why
sometimes I'm feelin' under ♪
♪ Gotta keep my faith
alive 'til love is found ♪
♪ Now ask yourself where is the love ♪
♪ Where is the love ♪
♪ Father Father Father help us ♪
♪ Send some guidance from above ♪
♪ 'Cause people got me
got me questioning ♪
♪ Where is the love ♪
♪ Sing with me y'all ♪
♪ One world one world ♪
♪ We only got one world one world ♪
♪ That's all we got one world one world ♪
♪ And something's wrong with it yeah ♪
♪ Something's wrong with it yeah ♪
♪ Something's wrong with
the wo-wo-world yeah ♪
♪ We only got one world one world ♪
♪ That's all we got ♪
♪ One world one world ♪